Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory10 Mss.B.B61.inventory10
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents P
  - Phillips, Harold C. (Box 70)
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 4; 1p.
  - Phillips, H., Jr. -- (American Philosophical Society) (Box 70)
    - To Boas, 1888 Nov. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Dec. 29; 2p.
  - Phillips, L. (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1933 Sept. 18; 1p
  - Phillips, N. (Box 70)
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 11; 1p
  - Phillips, T.W. Jr. (Box 70)
    - To Boas, 1940 Aug. 8; 1p
    - To Marshall, James E. enc. with above, 1940 July 31; 1p
  - Phillips, William (Box 70)
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 22
    - To Boas, 1916 Feb. 10
    - To Boas, 1919 Dec. 8; 1p
    - To Dixon, R.B., 1913 Dec. 22
  - Phillips Academy, Treasurer (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 15
  - Phily, Hoffman (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1906 Aug. 24
  - Philosophical Review (Box 70)
    See Creighton, J.E.
  - Philosophical Society, American (Box 70)
  - Phinney, Archie (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Nov. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Nov. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Sep. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Feb. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Feb. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 May 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Aug. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Nov. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 June 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Sept 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 18
    - To Boas, 1929 Sept 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Dec. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 21; 2p
    - Phinney, A. -- to FB, 1932 May 26
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov 13
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec 26
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Feb. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 May 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 Aug. 8; 4p
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Feb. 1; 1p
    - See FB open letter, 1934 Feb. 23
    - To Boas, 1934 Feb. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1934 May 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1934 July 6; 4p
    - To Boas, 1934 Sept 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 Jan. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 July 11; 3p
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 7; 2p
  - Phinney, M. (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1927 June 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Sept 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Sept 22; 2p
  - Photomart Corporation (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1935 Nov. 4; 1p
  - Pickenbach, N.E. (Box 70)
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 24; 1p
  - Pickens, W. (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1934 Feb. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Dec. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Feb. 2; 1p
  - Picker, J. (Box 70)
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 16; 1p
    - From Davidson, M.P., 1933 Dec. 11
    - To Davidson, M.P., 1933 Dec. 16; 1p
  - Pickering, E.C. (Box 70)
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 7; 3p
    - From Boas, 1916 Sept 27
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec. 7; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 Oct. 12
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 11; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 May 21; 3p
    - To Boas, 1916 Sept 5
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 13
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 19
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 28
    - To Boas, 1919 May 9
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 May 22; 1p
  - Pickhardt, Carl (Box 70)
    - To Boas, E.L., 1904 June 21; 1p
  - Pierce, C.C. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1919 June 6; 1p
  - Pierce, Henry Clay (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1904 Jan. 12; 2p
  - Pierce, P.B. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1900 Nov. 15
    - From Boas, 1901 May 27
    - From Boas, 1902 Feb. 13
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 22
    - To Boas, 1900 Mar. 12
    - To Boas, 1900 Apr. 10
    - To Boas, 1900 Aug. 6
    - To Boas, 1900 Nov. 14
    - To Boas, 1901 May 21
    - To Boas, 1901 Aug. 29
    - To Hodge, 1900 Oct. 8
    - From Andrews, H.A., 1901 Sept 3
  - Pierce, V. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1925 Nov. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Sept 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 28; 1p
  - Pierson, Violet W. (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1909 Sept 23
  - Pierson, W.W. Jr. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 5; 1p
  - Pietschman, R. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 6; 1p
  - Pi Gamma Mu, Inc. (Box 71)
    - See Allen, Leroy, 1932 Nov. 28
  - Pijoan, Joseph (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1921 Mar. 19; 3p
  - Pike, Victoria (Box 71)
    - To Sapir, E., 1937 June 8; 1p
  - Pilling, James C. (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1893 Jan. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1894 Oct. 27
    - To Boas, 1894 Nov. 15
    - To Boas, 1894 Dec. 11
  - Pillsbury, W.B. (Box 71)
    - See FB to Woodworth, R.S., 1931 Sept. 2
  - Pilsudski, B. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1916 Sept 28
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1908 May 20
    - To Boas, 1909 May 10
    - To Boas, 1909 June 8
    - To Boas, 1914 May 23
  - Piltman (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1898 Jan. 28
    - To Boas, 1898 Mar. 5
    - To Boas, 1898 Apr. 26
    - To Boas, 1898 May
  - Piltzburg, C. (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 21
  - Pinchot, Gifford (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 7
    - To Boas, 1912 Sept 9
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 4
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 16
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 4
  - Pine, J.B. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1916 June 5
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 11; 1p
    - To Cattell, J.M., 1918 Apr. 3; 1p
  - Pinson, Koppel S. (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 30; 1p
  - Pintner, R. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Dec. 7; 1p
  - Pinto (Box 71)
    See Roquette-Pinto
  - Pintus, Hedwig (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1932 July 15; 3p
    - To Boas, 1932 July 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 July 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 17; 2p
  - Pirk, H.B. (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1922 Sept 21; 2p
  - Pitkin, W.B. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1931 July 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 July 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 15; 1p
  - Pitman, Mason (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1935 Sept 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 May 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 May 19; 1p
  - Pittard, E. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 11; 3p
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Jan. 18; 2p
  - Pitus, M.C. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 16; 1p
  - Pizarro, Miguel (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1937 Sept 22
  - Placzek, Siegfried (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1939 Nov. 27; 1p
  - Der Plan einer Rassen-EnquC*te (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1934 Apr. 13; 2p
  - Planck, Max (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 13; 1p
  - Plaskow, E.H. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1933 May 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 May 23; 2p
  - Platt, O.H. (Box 71)
    - To Boass, 1902 Dec. 18; 1p
  - Platt, Philip (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1930 June 3; 1p
  - Platt, William (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 15; 1p
  - Plaut, A. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 May 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Dec. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 14; 1p
  - Pliester, R. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1928 June 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 June 25; 1p
  - Plimpton, Geo. A. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1889 Apr. 11
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 15; 3p
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 16; 2p
    - From Boas, 1907 May 4
    - From Boas, 1907 May 10
    - From Boas, 1907 May 22
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 20; 16 p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 10
    - To Boas from Ginn & Co., 1889 Apr. 10
    - To Boas, 1905 Jan. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 6
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 2
    - To Boas, 1906 May 6
    - To Boas, 1906 May 24
  - Ploetz, A. (Box 71)
    - 1912 Nov. 5
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 7
  - Plotkin, B. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1939 Aug. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 11
  - Plummer, John F. Jr. (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1897 Mar. 9
  - Podoloff, Jacob (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 3; 1p
  - Poffenberger, A.T. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 24; 1p
      - see FB to Dunn, and MacIver, 1934 Apr. 6
    - From Boas, 1934 June 8; 1p
      - see FB to Dunn, and MacIver, 1934 June 8; 2p
      - see FB to Dunn, L.C. and to MacIver & L.C., 1934 June 8
    - From Boas, 1934 June 12; 1p
      - see FB to Dunn, L.C. and to MacIver & L.C., 1936 Apr. 6; 1p
    - To Boas
      - see Keppel, F.P., 1930 Nov. 7
    - To Boas, 1930 Dec. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 21; 1p
      - see FB: Study, 1938 Apr. 4
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct. 18; 1p
  - Polakowsky (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1913 June 15; 3p
  - Poland, A.B. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1909 Feb. 6
    - To Boas, 1909 Feb. 10
    - From Anon., 1909 Dec. 31
  - Polar Kommission, Deutsche (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1885 June 27
  - Poling, D.A. (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1937 Sept. 5
  - Poll, Heinrich (Box 71)
    - 1935 Nov. 25, 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Sept 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 May 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 June 21; 2p
  - Pollak, G. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 21
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 19
  - Pollak, O. (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 25; 5p
  - Pollitzer, Alice K. (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 8
  - Pollitzer, S. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 5
  - Polson, Jes. K. (Box 71)
    - see FB open letter re Spain, 1938 Jan.
  - Pomfrot, J.E. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 15; 1p
  - Poniatowski, Stanislaw (Box 71)
    - To Boas8, 1936 Oct. 15; 1p
  - Pooler, Blanche F. (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1934 July 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Aug. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Aug. 10; 1p
  - Poore, Charles (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 7; 1p
  - Pope, Arthur U. (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1941 Sept. 8; 1p
  - Popper, W. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1925 Jan. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 Jan. 10; 1p
  - Pordeu, Edward (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 29; 1p
  - Porsild, M.P., 1923 May 27; 1p (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1923 Oct. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 May 27; 1p
  - Porte, G.A.H. (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1930 Dec. 15; 1p
  - Portello, J.S. (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1911 Aug. 1
  - Porter (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1906 Dec. 3
  - Porter, Cyrus S. (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1939 Nov. 16; 1p
  - Porter, Russell W. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1903 Dec. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1897 Mar. 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1897 Mar. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1897 May 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1894 May 27
    - To Boas, 1897 Oct. 31
    - To Boas, 1898 Mar. 11
    - To Boas, 1898 Mar. 28
    - To Boas, 1903 Dec. 5
  - Porter, William Townsend (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1903 Dec. 11
    - To Boas, 1894 May 27
    - To Boas, 1903 Dec. 5
  - Porterfield, Alan W. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 27; 1p
  - Porto Rico, Commissioner of agriculture and labor (Box 71)
    In Britton, N.L. #5
    - 1917 Sept. 11
  - Porto Rico, Governor of (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 6; 2p
  - Porto Rico Line (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1915 Apr. 23
  - Posen, F.L. (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1910 June 24
  - Posen, W.S. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1910 July 26
  - Poske, Fr. (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1886 Jan. 20
    - To Boas, 1886 Feb. 4
  - Posnansky, A. (Box 71)
    - From B9as, 1925 Mar. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Mar. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 5; 1p
  - Posner, L.S. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1933 May 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 May 27; 1p
  - Posposil, F. (Box 71)
    Southwest
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 July 23; 3p
  - Posselt, Erich (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Jan. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 18; 1p
  - Post, John A. (Box 71)
    - 1926 Nov. 15, 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 June 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Oct. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 May 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 June 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 10; 2p
  - Postural Difference in Native and Assimilated Immigrant Groups (Box 71)
    - 1935 Mar. 8, 3p
      See Gestures
      See Scenario Draft
  - Potter, J.C. (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1936 June 2; 1p
      See also TIME, EDITOR OF LETTERS
  - Potter, Russell (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Oct. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Oct. 14; 1p
  - Potter, W.B. (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1916 Jan. 10
  - Pottinger, David T. (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1941 Dec. 3; 1p
  - Pound, L. (Box 71)
    - To Folk-lore, enc. with Beckwith, M.W., 1923 May 9
  - Pound, Roscoe (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 May 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 May 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 May 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Aug. 15; 1p
  - Pourchet, Maria Julia, 1936 Apr. 14; 1p (Box 71)
    - 1936 June 19
    - From Boas, 1936 Sept 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Dec. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 31; 3p
    - To Boas, 1936 June 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 June 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 July 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 Sept 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Nov. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1937 Jan. 15; 1p
    - To Columbia U., Dept. Anthropology, 1936 Apr. 1; 2p
    - To Columbia U., Dept. Anthropology, 1936 Aug. 11; 1p
  - Pourhuge?, Silvan (Box 71)
    Hopi baskets
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 25
  - Powell, J.W. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1887 Nov. 16
    - From Boas, 1888 Feb. 9
    - From Boas, 1888 Feb. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1888 Aug. 8; 4p
    - From Boas, 1888 Nov.
    - From Boas, 1891 Oct. 19
    - From Boas, 1893 Jan. 18; 2p
    - From Boas, 1893 Jan. 30; 4p
    - From Boas, 1893 Mar. 19; 2p
    - From Boas, 1895 June 19
    - From Boas, 1895 July 28
    - From Boas, 1898 Nov. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1898 Dec. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1901 May 25
    - To Boas, 1887 Dec. 15
    - To Boas, 1888 Dec. 21
    - To Boas, 1890 Mar. 10
    - To Boas, 1895 June 7
    - To Boas, 1895 July 3
    - To Boas, 1895 Oct. 22
  - Powell, R.J. (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 17
  - Powell, T.R. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1917 Dec. 17
    - From Boas, 1917 Dec. 24
    - To Boas, 1917 Dec. 26
  - Power, A.W. (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1897 July 19
  - Power, L.G. (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1889 Apr. 27; 3p
    - To Boas, 1889 Nov. 25; 3p
  - Power, Mary D. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 16
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 11
  - Powis, A. & Son (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1927 May 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 May 19; 1p
  - Powleson, C.F. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1910 July 1
    - To Boas, 1910 June 27
    - To Boas, 1910 July 25
  - Poynts, Juliet Stuart (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1912 Sept 12
  - Prager, W.L. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1933 June 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 May 25; 1p
  - Prahl, Ferdinand (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1904 Dec. 2; 3p
  - Pramir [?], A. (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1923 June 15; 1p
  - Prats, Alardo (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 23; 3p
  - Pratt, (Dean's secretary, Columbia) (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1906 June 27
  - Pratt, Derrill (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1936 July 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Aug. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 July 18; 1p
  - Pratt, M.M. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1917 Oct. 30
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 24
  - "Pravda" (Box 71)
    See Olgin, Moissaye J.
  - Prentice, William Kelly (Box 71)
    - To Am. Coun. Learned Societies, 1941 July 12; 1p
    - enc. with Graves, M., 1941 July 22
  - Prentis, A. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec. 12; 1p
  - Prentis, H.W. (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 25; 1p
  - Prentiss, M. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 11; 1p
  - Presby, Frank H. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1906 Dec. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 10; 1p
    - per Day, Agent to Boas, E.L., 1906 Dec. 3; 1p
    - To Germanistic Soc. of Am., 1906 Mar. 20; 2p
  - Prescott, Harriet B. (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 12
  - Prest, W.H. (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1904 Apr. 9; 2p
  - Prestes, Luiz Carlos (Box 71)
    - See Coun. for Pan Am. Democ. enc. with McAvoy, C.T., 1904 Oct. 24
  - Preston, Cecile (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1926 Apr. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Apr. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Apr. 26; 1p
  - Prestorius, Emil (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1906 Oct. 14; 1p
  - Preuschen-Telmann, Hermione von (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 23; 3p
  - Preuss, K. Th. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 25
    - From Boas, 1910 May 19
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 June 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 5, Nov. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Feb. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 June 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 31; 4p
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 5; 4p
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 13
    - To Boas, 1910 May 6
    - To Boas, 1910 June 1
    - To Boas, 1911 Dec. 19
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 2
    - To Boas, 1920 Jan. 30; 4pand
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 July 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 July 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Aug. 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Sept 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 July 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 May 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 May 25; 1p
  - Preussische Akademie der Wissenschaften (Box 71)
    see Lüders, Heinrich
  - Preussische Staatsbibliothek (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1926 May 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 July 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 13; 1p
      See Kruss, Hugo
      Feldkamp, Heinrich
      Kuhnert, Ernst
  - Prezzolini, G. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1935 May 8; 1p
    - To Colucci, C., 1935 Feb. 4; 1p
    - To Colucci, C., 1935 Feb. 7; 1p
    - To Colucci, C., 1935 Feb.; 1p
  - Pribham, A.F. (Box 71)
    - From Baumhackl, 1926 July 8
  - Price, H.B. (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1941 Feb. 28; 1p
  - Price, Laurence M. (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 May 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1940 Apr. 20; 1p
  - Price, Thos. R. (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1897 May 19; 1p
  - Price-Mars (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1941 Feb. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Feb. 18; 1p
  - Priest, G.M. (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 1
    - To Frachtenberg, 1917 Nov. 1
  - "Primitive Art" (Box 71)
    See Gallimard, M.
  - Prince, J. Dyneley (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1903 Dec. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1908 Dec. 21; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 Dec. 10
    - From Boas, 1917 Dec. 20
    - From Boas, 1917 Dec. 24
    - From Boas, 1917 Dec. 31; 4p
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 May 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Oct. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Oct. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Nov. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1900 Mar. 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1903 Dec. 14 and 1905 Feb. 21
    - To Boas, 1905 Feb. 27
    - To Boas, 1905 May 2
    - To Boas, 1905 May 16
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 12
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 26
    - To Boas, 1917 Dec. 21
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Mar. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 July 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Jan. 4; 3p
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 3; 3p
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 17; 2p
  - Prince, L. Bradford (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 9
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 29; 2
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 9
  - Prince, Mary C. (Box 71)
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec.17
  - Prince Rupert, B.C. Elec. Pow. House (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1939 Nov. 1; 1p
    - See FB to Little, J.J., 1939 Nov. 13
  - Princeton University. Secretary (Box 71)
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 21; 1p
      same to Brown Univ., Univ. of Cincinnati Columbia Univ., Wash. Univ. of Chicago
  - Printed material - American Committee for Democracy and Intellectual Freedom, 1938-1941
    Includes printed copy of the Manifesto on Freedom of Science (1938) with full list of signers.
  - Printed material - Emergency Society for German/Austrian Science and Art, 1921-1927
  - Printed material - Germanistic Society of America, 1910-1929
  - Pritchett, H.S. (Box 72)
    - From Boas, 1906 June 4
    - From Boas, 1906 Aug. 18
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 16
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 16
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 16
    - From Boas, 1907 May 6
    - From Boas, 1907 May 15
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 10; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 9; 4p
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 20; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 17; 1p
    - To B9as, 1905 May 3
    - To B9as, 1906 June 6
    - To B9as, 1906 Aug. 20
    - To B9as, 1918 Apr. 3; 4p
    - To B9as, 1919 Mar. 24; 1p
    - To B9as, 1920 June 18; 3p
    - From Putnam, F.W., 1906 Aug. 20
  - Pritt (Box 72)
    - To Hays, A.G., 1940 Mar. 4
  - Prittwitz u. Gaffron, Germen Ambassador to U.S. (Box 72)
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 24; 1p
  - Problem of Selective Migration (Box 72)
    - 1938 Dec. 31, 1p
  - Probst (Box 72)
    - Open Letter re Kallmann, Franz, 1936 Dec. 23; 1p
  - Products Exchange Corporation (Box 72)
    - From Boas, 1921 Nov. 30; 1p
    - To Boas (see Ohsol, J.G.), 1921 Nov. 29; 1p
  - Proffitt, C.G. (Box 72)
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 July 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Feb. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 May 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 July 14; 2p
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb.; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Mar. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Apr. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 May 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 July 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Sep. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Dec. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 June 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 June 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 June 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 June 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 June 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 15; 1p
  - Progressive Education Assn. Commission on Intercultural Education (Box 72)
    - Minutes, 1937 Mar. 29; 3p
    - Petition, 1937 Mar. 31
  - Prokosch, Eduard (Box 72)
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 May 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Jan. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Sept 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 27; 1p